photoshop-kopona.com 2019-06-30

# Privacy Policy

**Introduction**  
photoshop-kopona.com respect the privacy of the visitors to this web site and any co-branded, mirrored, or successor sites (the "Website") and are committed to protecting their privacy. photoshop-kopona.com has established this Privacy Policy Statement to inform you of our policies and practices regarding how we collect personal identifiable information from you, how we use and disclose it, and your rights with respect to such information. By using this Website, you acknowledge and agree to the terms and conditions of this photoshop-kopona.com Privacy Policy Statement ("Privacy Policy"). If you do not agree to these terms and conditions, please do not use this Website. 

We reserve the right to change or modify our privacy practices that are described herein from time to time simply by posting a revised Privacy Policy on this Website. Any such change shall be effective immediately upon posting of the revised Privacy Policy on this Website. We reserve the right to make the revised or changed Privacy Policy effective for information we already have about you, as well as any information we receive in the future. We encourage you to refer to this Privacy Policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy practices. 

**Privacy Policy**  
Like many websites, we gather information about how visitors use this Website. In general, you can visit many of the web pages on this Website without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. We, however, may track your Internet Protocol (IP) address and other anonymous information from your web browser for trends and statistics (including, but not limited to, browser version, pages requested and pages visited), but you will remain anonymous unless you provide us with personal information during your visit to this Website or during an earlier or subsequent visit and we are able to link your IP address between your current visit and one of these other visits. 

We also work with service providers who use tracking technologies to serve ads across the Internet or track email communication response rates on our behalf. These companies may collect personal informationabout your visits to this Website and your interaction with our communications, including advertising. 

In addition to anonymous information, we also collect personal information from you at this Website when you voluntarily submit it to us. We request personal information from you (which may include your nik, email address) when you:   
* Complete a registration; * Submit materials to our Website; 

We also collect information about your activities on and through this Website from our third party business partners, suppliers, vendors and other agents. 

You may choose not to provide us with any personal information. In such event, you can still access and use many portions of this Website; however, you will not be able to access and use those portions of this Website or the services available on or through this Website that require your personal information. 

**Advertising / Online Tracking**   
photoshop-kopona.com may use online advertising networks to serve ads on third-party websites. You can opt out of receiving targeted ads from many websites by using the opt-out tools available through some browser settings ("Do Not Track") or via the AdChoices icon on any advertisements. Please note that if you opt out, you may still receive online advertising, but the ads that you receive will be generic and not based on your online preferences or behavior. 

Providers of advertising technologies, including Google and other advertising networks, use personal data to display personalized advertising and collect statistics on conversions. 

**Your Consent**   
As a condition to using the photoshop-kopona.com, we require your approval to collect this data. By visiting https://photoshop-kopona.com/ or any of our affiliated sites, you agree that our site may collect and use this information as stated in this privacy policy. If we change this privacy policy, we will post the changes on this page. 

**Using Information**   
We may use the information we collect to:   
* Customize and/or personalize your communications, surfing, viewing and/or shopping experience; * Better respond to your customer service inquiries; * Communicate with you about your purchase, account information, or customer service needs; * Communicate with you about our products and events, and for other promotional purposes; * Improve our business; * Administer contests, promotions, surveys or other website features; * Perform any other lawful acts except for those acts expressly prohibited by the terms and conditions set forth herein. 

**Sharing Information**   
Except as expressly set forth herein, we do not loan, give away, sell, distribute or rent your personal information to any third party. We will disclose your personal information to third parties if you have previously consented to such disclosures and in special circumstances, including, but not limited to, the sale of photoshop-kopona.com; the due diligence in connection with a potential sale of photoshop-kopona.com; any bankruptcy, insolvency or liquidation of photoshop-kopona.com, or in other similar circumstances.  
We also may disclose personal information about you upon request by the government; in response to a court order; when required by law or when we believe in good faith is required by law; to enforce our Privacy Policy, terms and conditions or other agreements on this Website; upon your request; or to contact, identify or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with our or others. rights or property.  
We may also provide aggregated, non-personally identifiable information to third parties for any legal purposes whatsoever. 

**Protecting Your Information**   
We use commercially reasonable efforts to safeguard and secure your personal information while stored on our computer systems. We use a variety of industry standard security measures, including encryption and authentication tools, to maintain the confidentiality of your personal information. Your personal information is stored behind industry standard firewalls and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who are authorized to access such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. Regardless of these efforts by us, no system connected to the internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. 

**Cookies**   
This Website uses cookies. A cookie is a small, removable data file that is stored by your web browser on your computer.:   
Cookies allow * Present relevant content to you when you visit this Website; * Analyze visitor behavior; and * Facilitate other similar type of activities.   
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your web browser settings. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your visit to this Website more efficient and enjoyable, and in some cases, some of our services will not function or will function with limited capability.   
We use cookies to personalise ads and to analyse our traffic.We also share information about your use of our site with our social media, advertising and analytics partners who may combine it with other information that you've provided to them or that they've collected from your use of their services. 

**Other Websites**  
When browsing this Website, you may be directed to other websites that are beyond our control. These other websites may use cookies and pixel tags, collect data, or solicit personal information. Even though photoshop-kopona.com may be affiliated with these websites, we have no control over them or how they collect, distribute or otherwise use your personal information or how they safeguard and secure your personal information. photoshop-kopona.com is not responsible or liable for the conduct, policies or actions of the owners of such websites or the content displayed on these websites. These websites are linked to this Website only for your convenience and you access them at your own risk. 

**Questions and Feedback** We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about this Privacy Policy and our privacy practices. Please send us feedback pertaining to these matters or any other issue you may have with photoshop-kopona.com or this Website. You may contact us using the contact form located at [**feedback**](https://photoshop-kopona.com/?do=feedback "feedback")
